{
    "id": "4d58adf560934fc2b5c023ea28e9f604",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met him ......................... a club.",
            "description": "We use at to indicate position at a point.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is some water ......................... the bottle.",
            "description": "We use in to indicate position inside something.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car broke down .......................... the way to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I read an interesting article ........................ the magazine.",
            "description": "We say in a book or a magazine.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She spent the whole day ............................. the bedroom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are hungry, there is a banana ............................. the fridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They are moving .............................. the suburbs.",
            "description": "We use to to indicate direction.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you take the children .............................. school?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can call me ................................ six.",
            "description": "We use at with clock time.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The Prime Minister spoke ............................ television last night.",
            "description": "We use on with television.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you recognize him ............................... this photo?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Bangalore is ............................... the South of India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}